{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948227236","data":{"timestamp":" 946948227236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948235669","data":{"timestamp":" 946948235669"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" d970522f-be3e-4469-8bf2-d387cdeaec38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948235892","data":{"timestamp":" 946948235892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" d970522f-be3e-4469-8bf2-d387cdeaec38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948236855","data":{"timestamp":" 946948236855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" d970522f-be3e-4469-8bf2-d387cdeaec38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948238128","data":{"timestamp":" 946948238128"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" d970522f-be3e-4469-8bf2-d387cdeaec38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948240992","data":{"timestamp":" 946948240992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" d970522f-be3e-4469-8bf2-d387cdeaec38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948241836","data":{"timestamp":" 946948241836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" d970522f-be3e-4469-8bf2-d387cdeaec38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948242149","data":{"timestamp":" 946948242149"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" d970522f-be3e-4469-8bf2-d387cdeaec38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948243382","data":{"timestamp":" 946948243382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" d970522f-be3e-4469-8bf2-d387cdeaec38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948246854","data":{"timestamp":" 946948246854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" d970522f-be3e-4469-8bf2-d387cdeaec38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948247837","data":{"timestamp":" 946948247837"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" d970522f-be3e-4469-8bf2-d387cdeaec38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948248090","data":{"timestamp":" 946948248090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" d970522f-be3e-4469-8bf2-d387cdeaec38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948249033","data":{"timestamp":" 946948249033"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" d970522f-be3e-4469-8bf2-d387cdeaec38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948251868","data":{"timestamp":" 946948251868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" d970522f-be3e-4469-8bf2-d387cdeaec38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948252902","data":{"timestamp":" 946948252902"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" d970522f-be3e-4469-8bf2-d387cdeaec38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948253375","data":{"timestamp":" 946948253375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" d970522f-be3e-4469-8bf2-d387cdeaec38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948257434","data":{"timestamp":" 946948257434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" d970522f-be3e-4469-8bf2-d387cdeaec38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948257488","data":{"timestamp":" 946948257488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" d970522f-be3e-4469-8bf2-d387cdeaec38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948277910","data":{"timestamp":" 946948277910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948280051","data":{"timestamp":" 946948280051"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948283908","data":{"timestamp":" 946948283908"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948286294","data":{"timestamp":" 946948286294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948288790","data":{"timestamp":" 946948288789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948290621","data":{"timestamp":" 946948290621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948293420","data":{"timestamp":" 946948293420"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948295597","data":{"timestamp":" 946948295597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948297402","data":{"timestamp":" 946948297402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948298096","data":{"timestamp":" 946948298096"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948298610","data":{"timestamp":" 946948298609"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948299452","data":{"timestamp":" 946948299452"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" JIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948300360","data":{"timestamp":" 946948300360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948300576","data":{"timestamp":" 946948300576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948300963","data":{"timestamp":" 946948300963"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948301760","data":{"timestamp":" 946948301760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948304699","data":{"timestamp":" 946948304698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948305017","data":{"timestamp":" 946948305016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948305722","data":{"timestamp":" 946948305722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" START_WALIISHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948306837","data":{"timestamp":" 946948306837"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" WALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948309122","data":{"timestamp":" 946948309122"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948309125","data":{"timestamp":" 946948309125"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948314262","data":{"timestamp":" 946948314262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948344640","data":{"timestamp":" 946948344639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948347281","data":{"timestamp":" 946948347280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948349170","data":{"timestamp":" 946948349170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948349920","data":{"timestamp":" 946948349920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948350729","data":{"timestamp":" 946948350728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" WALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948351446","data":{"timestamp":" 946948351446"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948351937","data":{"timestamp":" 946948351936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948352163","data":{"timestamp":" 946948352162"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948352607","data":{"timestamp":" 946948352607"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948352976","data":{"timestamp":" 946948352975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948353106","data":{"timestamp":" 946948353105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948353194","data":{"timestamp":" 946948353194"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_041014"," gameId":" 8b812663-c58c-4591-ad1a-4ea83d8efc50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}